It has happened a little neighbor since last time.
Yes some.
I have to get the body ready.
I've started here.
These plates and this door are done.
The foundation is clear but it must be directed.
It is a bit wavy after the English wheel.
It should be directed and smoothed out with armored file before starting to grind.
I have also made the moldings that will sit over the joints.
It's a front list, here.
I have had to shape it a bit because the convertible to lie against.
So I've had to lower it a bit.
This list is measured adapted.
It sits so tight so it can hardly be removed.
There is a screw bracket at the forefront.
So you attach it there and also to the back.
The strip is attached like this and then it is angled in place at the forefront.
From the beginning, this is a Volvo Amazon List.
As I have been directed because it has been bent in all directions.
Then I have heated the strip and stretch it out so it becomes completely straight.
Then you have to weld this one so it has something to attach in.
It can be tricky as it is thin material in stainless steel.
It goes well if you are careful.
It is the same type of strip but I have narrowed it so it gets pointed.
And got another shape at the bottom.
I have done this because the joint is much more pointed.
Then there had been air in between.
Now I have made the list a little narrower.
The width up here is the same.
The strip then becomes narrower all the way down.
-You have dressed the entire rear!
Well it went better than expected actually.
-This was paper last time I was here?
Yes it was cardboard.
Since then I have finished the inner frame.
I finished it only then the painting I frame.
Then you template the frame and cut a plate.
It will be a long plate.
This plate has been elected in one piece.
And here is the cormorant.
It is not so easy when you are alone and should roll such a long plate in the English wheel.
Do not have friends who show up here?
Yes, but they don't like to work.
You reinforce by adding an angle profile at the whole frame.
I attach the plate with welding bars so I get stiffness in the plate so I can roll the plate back and forth.
When I start rolling the plate, it becomes stiffer.
Then everything should be fitted.
Everything is hand -knocked around all falsaries.
It is not possible to do with a machine so it is the hammer that applies.
-What job!
-The difficult is to make two equal sides.
Making one is easier but the other must be equal.
I do not build this body that other car builders do.
They build fish skeletons in wood with wooden boards and then shape the plate after that.
Then you can oppose the plate and check that it fits.
I don't like working with wood ...
Then I would rather do this and template until it gets right.
It may take longer but it doesn't matter.
Should you collide with this car, you have to make the parts because they cannot be purchased.
The lock to the door sits here on the inside.
It's sitting here.
Now there is a spring here but it will not be needed when there is a rubber list here.
Then the door springs automatically.
Possibly there will be gas pistons or if there is to be a lock in a fixed position.
It works amazingly well.
-Shelt crazy what a job!
There is a lot of millimeter fit.
-This you have done this too.
Yes it is the bottom plate against the frame
Since the frame swings like this, it would have been difficult to get to the line.
Then I thought it was nicer to put in a bit and get a straight line.
Which is consistent with this line.
Then there are 5 of these that reinforce.
All the way down.
We have previously seen a template in cardboard.
These are made of stainless steel and I have welded the end together.
I will glue screws on the back.
Which is worn into the holes and screwed up.
Here on the edge, a friend has made small brass hats coming ...
In the next stage it is ...
... the doors and torpedo.
The torpedo is just a basic construction so far.
Here, reinforcement beams should be put down like this.
So we a possible crash with a deer, moose or a passenger car.
So it should be a support up here.
So it can be folded down.
And don't go along so you sit safely.
For the doors I have made a template.
I will knock the plate around.
So I get a swing that goes together with the torpedo something here.
The plate from the torpedo will be curved and then the plates meet about here.
The door will follow the line and then down.
The other plate will be in line with the door.
The shape continues up in the dashboard all the way away to the other door.
The entire rounding on the torpedo will be hand -knocked.
I have made a special tool.
I squeeze it on the plate and knock around.
I have grooved it so it attaches to the plate and does not slip away.
The length I have adapting so you can make a turn without it getting angular.
We do this instead.
Attach this one.
That's how.
Then you have to knock the last one.
Also bend with a pliers.
Then you get the right round and then you have to move the pliers each after.
Then it will be the same rounding all the way.
It will be bent a little so it goes in all the way.
Then it becomes a soft line all the way.
It is semi -hard aluminum.
I don't want too soft for then ...
... then there will be no hardness in it and then it widens too much.
-Now we have a sound that made a comeback.
Now it sounds again.
The fluorescent lamp also wants to be included in film.
Yes the fluorescent lamp lives its own life in the garage.
-Yes it is quiet then it starts to crack.
When it comes to the interior, I have made a chair to begin with.
To see what can fit.
It is a prototype to be cut down so it becomes easier to step in and out.
Then make one to a chair.
This is the padding that will be used.
It will not look like this but will be in black leather.
Even leather here that will go around the edge.
A little of the aluminum will be visible because I want to share the raw material left.
A wall will be manufactured behind the chairs.
And the wall will swing as much as the body.
Here there will be a couple of speakers.
If it is possible to hear over the main but we will see.